JavaScript must be enabled for the BookDigits website to display properly.

Please enable JavaScript and then reload the page.

clear

[Sign In](https://bookdigits.com/login)  /  [Sign Up](https://bookdigits.com/register)

Congratulations, you just met your reading goal for 2024!

share / hide

Come check out ScreenDigits, our companion site for tracking the movies and shows you watch!

Privacy Policy

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site.  
  
When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  

* To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
* To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
* To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
* To administer a contest, promotion, survey, or other site feature

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent.

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enable the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and remember certain information.  
  
We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.  
  
All users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account and going to the "Settings" page.

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our website's privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page and update the Privacy Policy modification date below.  
  
This policy was last modified on May 9, 2013.

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.  

© 2024 BookDigits  /  Created by Bennett Gavrish
